spiceupyourblog.com 2010-08-15

# Privacy Policy | Spice Up Your Blog

Privacy Policy for www.spiceupyourblog.com

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at Paul@spiceupyourblog.com.

At www.spiceupyourblog.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.spiceupyourblog.com and how it is used.

Log Files  
Like many other Web sites, www.spiceupyourblog.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
www.spiceupyourblog.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

DoubleClick DART Cookie  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.spiceupyourblog.com.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.spiceupyourblog.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....  
Google Adsense  
Clickbank  
Chitika  
Amazon

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.spiceupyourblog.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.spiceupyourblog.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.spiceupyourblog.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

* * *

**Did You Like This Post ? Click _Like_ Below To Let Us And Your Friends Know - Thanks !**

* * *

**Subscribe To The[ _Rss Feed_](http://feeds.feedburner.com/spiceupyourblog) Or Recieve The Latest Posts By Email**

**Write About Or Link To This Post On Your Blog - Easy Links :**  
Link Directly To This Post :  
  
Link To The Homepage :  

**Hey ! People That Read This Post Also Loved These Posts**

Still Looking For Something ?

Search This Blog

Custom Search 

Important Must Read Before Posting A Comment

In order to keep our comments Do-Follow we have some guidelines you need to follow.   
Do not put links in the body of your comment as it will automatically be blocked !   
Asking a question ? Make sure to tick the subscribe to comments by email box to be alerted of the reply.
